hash
Wars I love you so much Craigslist and
the reason is is because you posted this
ad for the
wangcaster
yeah that's
aw
no the best way to play a d
[Music]
flat I know I know
they're not all
gold yep that's a dick shaped guitar
guys that's um the biggest dick in the
room is now no longer the guy playing
Stairway to Heaven in the Guitar
Center in honor of this Brave new
invention tonight's hashtag is schlong
songs sometimes I have to explain to my
mom what it is I get paid to
do so examples of schlong songs would be
glory whole days taint nothing like the
real thing hell's balls I'm going to put
60 seconds on the clock and go yes Neil
purple
[Laughter]
vein oh oh oh oh bye Prince Albert
punch Michelle to my window yes punch
Dan mama said suck you
out Point still Bron theme from
Shaft
Michelle Can't Touch
piss Point Neil Tangled Up In pubes yes
points Dan wrecking balls in my
mouth you could have stopped at wrecking
balls but I'll give you points anyway
for going the extra mile Michelle Star
Spangled boner
yeah